i wanted to tell you the story because
it's a true story it happened i was in
seattle washington and i was taking the
red-eye flight okay you know the red-eye
flight you get on the plane at 12 30 at
night and you fly overnight now you
think you're gonna sleep you go wow i'm
gonna sleep on this plane but i have a
problem i don't know if you've been on a
plane lately if you have you know that
airline seats are faa regulated to be
16 inches wide that's what the
requirement is now 16 inches for a seat
look at me people
i'm 44 in the waist
even if you divide for front and back 44
don't go into 16. do you know what i'm
talking about i i can't put both cheeks
down okay you know i said no i'm not
going to be able to sleep and so i was
exhausted i finally got home to my home
port tampa florida got in my car drove
to lakeland florida where my wife and i
have a little house i was absolutely
exhausted so what did i do i went right
to bed went to bed fell asleep
8 30 in the morning slept all the way
till 12 30 at night now you have to
understand i need to tell you this
um i take a lot of medications
okay
i take 15 pills because of my heart
condition i take 15 pills every day now
if my wife were here she would be in the
back she would put her hands up and she
would say you tell them the truth okay
here's the truth i do take 15 pills
every day three of them were given to me
by doctors
12 were given to me by people like you
around the country who said if you'll
take this you'll get better okay that
that's that's the deal
i have a friend gordon douglas he he
gets these he gets shark cartilage
tablets have you heard of shark
cartilage he buys them from a canadian
veterinary supply house okay
yeah you think canadian meds are cheap
try canadian veterinarian meds they're
much better okay
shark cartilage and he sends them to me
is the shark cartilage helping your
heart i don't know i am swimming faster
than i've ever swam before and
and when i eat my eyes roll back in my
head but
unless you get the discovery channel you
wouldn't get that and so anyway so i
take that i have two ladies from the
essential oil companies the two major
essential oil i know you're in the room
i smell thieves oil okay i know you're
here okay great ladies who make me pills
they actually get this you if you're in
this you know this they buy empty pill
capsules they put droplets of ancient
biblical oils in there they send them to
me through the mail which i believe is a
federal offense okay
and i take them i don't question it i
can't pronounce any of the names of the
oils in fact the only oil name that i
know is i know that both of them put
three drops of frankincense oil have you
heard of frankincense okay i i have two
my background in in school i majored in
greek and philosophy and religion so i
know a little bit about frankincense
from the christmas story we know gold
frankincense and frankincense is an oil
to prepare you for your burial
which kind of bothers me that they're
putting that in my get better oil i
asked my wife i said why do you think
they're putting frankincense in my oil
she said they're hedging their bets
i said what do you mean by that she said
think about it it's kind of like the
person who goes to the veterinarian
who's also the taxidermist that way
either way you get your dog back you
know and so that's the concept so anyway
the story is i had flown this red-eye
flight i fell asleep i didn't wake up
until 12 30 at night i miss my nine
o'clock in the morning pills i miss my
nine o'clock at night pills and it
freaked me out because i know that my
heart is going to be off the chain real
quick i quietly got out of bed i didn't
want to wake up my wife i love my wife
that's the kind of husband i am i got
out quietly went into the kitchen didn't
even turn on the light because the light
could shine into the bedroom and wake
her up i didn't want to wake her up
that's the kind of husband that i am
that's the way i wrote that's how i do
it okay and so i quietly i open the
refrigerator door just to have enough
refrigerator light to begin to take my
15 pills now i'm telling you right now
you can't take 15 pills at once i've
tried i take mine in like three groups
of seven
and so
not a big math crowd right here
go home school and so
i start taking my pills in the taking of
my pills in the semi-darkness i look
down apparently i have dropped two pills
on the floor now we have young kids at
our house we believe if something falls
on the floor you have a short amount of
time a window of time in which to pick
them up and they are still considered
clean are you with me at our house
that's 45 minutes okay and so
i i reached out i pick up the pills dust
them off pop them in my mouth swallow
them down went back slid into bed as
quietly as i could because that's the
kind of husband i am
and i'm laying there trying to get back
to sleep
but i'm so tired and my body clock is
off have you ever been so tired you
can't sleep
what is the deal with that where's a
medical person is any dog is there a
doctor or a nurse in here anyway nobody
will claim it tonight will you okay
right
i don't understand is how can you be too
tired to sleep it makes no sense i've
never been so hungry i couldn't eat
right
i've i i've never been i have got a
piece so bad i can't paint you know what
i'm saying
i said that last night in st louis an
old guy shouts out well you've never had
a kidney stone and so that's
that's what he said okay
and i'm just i'm exhausted so i'm laying
there trying to go to sleep now i've
heard about people who count sheep okay
you know they count sheep i don't know
how to count sheep never raise sheep uh
again a little bit of that religion
background and do so i like to go
through the books to the bible i like to
just count them you know what i mean
count the books of the bible one genesis
2 exodus 3 leviticus 4 numbers you know
do all 35 40 of them and and go through
that
not a big theological crowd either put
that down okay
and go through that and as i'm going
through the books of the bible there i i
went quickly i started to get
indigestion i went quickly from
indigestion to an upset stomach quickly
from an upset stomach to pain now when i
reached pain i realized that i should
not suffer alone can i get a witness
meant can i get a witness okay
and and i turn to my wife the love of my
life we have been married 33 years
consecutively okay
and and i turned to her and i shook her
arm and i said baby wake up i'm not
feeling well at all to which my wife the
love of my life my childhood sweetheart
opens one eye and says
roll over and go to sleep you'll feel
fine in the morning let me say that was
not the level of care i expect after 33
faithful years
and i started to get mad i started
getting angry and i said no i'm not
gonna do it
what
would jesus do
i thought he would send her to hell
right now is what he would do she'd be
gone
no no no no i said i said jesus would
give her a second chance can i get a
yeah you know what i'm saying okay and
so so i thought about this and i said i
have got to put this in a way i've got
to wake her up in a way that she can buy
into having empathy for me now some of
you are saying mike you sound like a
counselor background no no counseling
background at all but my wife was my
wife has her bachelor's degree in
counseling and her master's degree in
orchestral conducting my wife is a
female orchestra conductor i know it's
impressive but talk about unemployable
there it is okay
[Music]
but i'm not bitter it was 120 000 that
one day we'll be glad we were paying for
and so anyway
she used to wake me up at all hours of
the night when she was pregnant
my wife was infatuated with our child's
kicking
and she would wake me up in the middle
of the night and say baby feel this she
would grab my hand she would put it on
her stomach and she'd go wait
and i would wait and she'd go okay wait
and about 20 minutes later she'd go
there there did you feel that and i
would always go
oh wow
that was amazing but i'm going to be
honest with you i'm probably going to
get kicked out of the men's club for
saying this i never felt nothing nothing
nothing not a zip zilch but i always
pretended i did why because i loved her
and i loved the child okay i think it
ought to be reciprocal i reached over i
shook her arm i said baby wake up feel
my stomach something is kicking
to which she opens up one eye and says
quit whining
out of the mouth of a christian woman
now i'm mad now i'm laying right over on
my side of the bed right there against
the i'm just talking myself i'm not
whining i know when i'm whining oh i can
i'm a man i know how to whine we were
trained in it when we were young i know
i know how to i'm not just going to get
better in the morning i know what i'm
going to get better in the morning i'm
not going to get better in fact i hope i
die
i hope i die to prove to you and your
mother
finally i couldn't take it anymore i got
up i got dressed i got in my car drove
down to the emergency room they took me
right in and started scanning my body
with an ultrasound machine you know
those machines that look inside you
they're asking me questions mr williams
have you had an operation recently i
said no last operation i had was 27
years ago why do you ask and he turned
the screen toward me he moved the probe
right in here he said mr williams if
you'd had an operation we'd almost
believe that somehow they had
inadvertently accidentally of course
left two sponges in you there are two
sponges a medical size six inch medical
don't get ahead of me you already know
more than i knew at the time two six
inch medical sponges in your intestinal
tract the young doctor leans over and he
says one of the sponges looks like a
dinosaur okay
don't get ahead of me don't get ahead of
me
they do a little more scanning than they
left the room they went out to that you
know how they have it in the emergency
room they have that island of computers
out there where they go out and look up
on google to see what they think you
might have and
of course i'm on obamacare so i get a
free second opinion from bing and so
when they went out there i got out my
phone i called my wife i woke her up for
a third time i said i'm not just whining
i'm not just gonna get better in the
morning i have two sponges in me six
inch sponges in my intestinal tract and
one of the sponges looks like a dinosaur
to which my wife the love of my life 33
years
says to me
we went to the dollar store today
have you ever had somebody join your
conversation that had no idea what you
were talking about
i said baby wake up i'm at the emergency
room the er er i am here i'm here three
doctors are in the room i have a t-rex
in my intestines i could i could care
less where you went shopping today
she said i'm not asleep silly we went to
the doctor today and your middle son
coleman with his dollar bought four
little green pills when you throw them
in water six minutes later they expand a
six inch foam dinosaurs
he lost two of the pills
i said i will call you back